That was close!
Forgive the intrusion.
Inside me?!
My, it's cozier than I expected.
Gross! I don't have any senses, but this still feels gross!
Get out!
We can't have that.
Even by doing this,
you can't completely
control my movements!
Oh, I don't intend to match strengths with you.
As long as I can dampen
your motions a little bit...
...we can finish this up.
Are you hurt?
I bumped my forehead.
Alphonse Elric,
you're coming with us...
to see our boss.
Having you come after us would be problematic.
Maybe I'll just crush
one of your legs.
Let's go!
W-Wait!
Man cannot obtain anything
without first sacrificing something.
In order to obtain anything,
something of equal value is required.
That is alchemy's
Law of Equivalent Exchange.
At the time, we believed that
to be the true way of the world.
So, where are the boys?
Alphonse-kun was
taken away by someone,
and Edward-kun gave chase.
While you were here,
and you just let them go?
This had been
dropped in the garden.
Devil's Nest?
Apparently it is a bar
outside of town.
You're worried about
Alphonse-kun, huh?
This wasn't your doing, was it?
If it were, I wouldn't have had them kidnap him here, would I?
Beyond the forest...
out in the rest of the world, the fighting continues.
The coals of the quarrel are stoked by malice;
sparks keep flying out,
and it spreads ever farther.
Why don't people
try to end the strife?
Not everyone secludes themselves in the middle of a forest,
thinking of nothing
but alchemy, like you do.
As long as they continue to
seek the Philosopher's Stone,
sooner or later, disaster is going to befall those two.
Why won't you stop them?
Those two will come upon their answer on their own.
Whatever answer that answer turns out to be,
at least it will be an answer different from your ideals.
You still can't bring
yourself to believe?
You and I are different, after all.
Both in our way of life
and in our alchemy.
You're going, then?
Yes.
Farewell, Izumi.
I doubt we will ever
see each other again.
Sorry about this.
I have to be on the lookout.
I know it must be icky having me inside,
but try to put up with it.
It's okay, I've gotten used to it.
Just don't touch my bloodseal, okay?
I won't be able to stay in this world if you do.
Say, Mister, how come
you became Chimeras?
We all used to be soldiers
a long time ago.
We were severely injured
on the battlefield out east.
While we were half-dead, we were taken to the military's lab facilities,
where we were turned into experimental subjects.
The 5th Laboratory...
That's right.
And it was Greed-san who
broke us out of that laboratory.
Greed...
That man gave us a place where we could live.
That I did.
See, this is a hangout where folks who,
for whatever little reason,
can no longer go on
living out in the open.
Tucker-san...
Tucker-san, are you...
D-Don't misunderstand.
I'm not here because I want to be.
The doctor here is the only one
who can cure us Chimeras, you see.
Whoa, this is awesome!
Dr. Tucker, it's just like you said.
He really is hollow.
I-I'm not the one who had you kidnapped, you understand.
Nice to meet you, boy.
The name's Greed.
Let's be friends.
An Uroboros tattoo...
You know about this?
That speeds things up.
Then you're friends with those
other people, like Envy and Lust?
Nope. They're more like
my enemies than my friends.
Then why are you doing this?
Al... was it?
How does it feel to be just
a spirit body—someone who can't die?
Transmuting an individual soul
and bonding it to some other object—
in other words, never getting hungry, growing tired, or growing any older.
That's what folks call
eternal life, isn't it?
Eternal life...
You kidnapped me because that's what you want?
I have powerful appetites, you see.
I want money! I want women!
Status, too! Fame, too!
I want all that this world has!
And that goes for eternal life, too.
You understand me?
You have the potential for that.
You're going to
cooperate with me.
If you refuse, I'm still going to get the secret of your soul,
even if I have to dismantle you.
What nonsense.
You really are a bad person after all, Mister.
It's up to you whether or not you act tough,
but there's no one who's going to rescue you from this situation.
My brother was together with me back there.
I'm sure he's on his way here.
That's not possible.
I beat him senseless.
You really are a bad person!
You let your guard down!
I'll take care of these chains with alchemy—
You'll do what?
Hey, relax, huh?
Oh, sorry, Martel.
I forgot you were in there.
I like a guy who can
set his mind to something.
But that's not going to
do you any good at all.
If you want to defeat me,
you'll have to do
something like this.
How could you do that?!
You guys are friends, aren't you?!
That makes me dead once.
Hey, can't you be a little neater when you do that?
Terribly sorry.
Even with this body,
I'm not exactly immortal.
Brother!
Pardon me for intruding.
S-Sensei!
Sweetheart, who are you?
A housewife!
Hold up, Edward Elric!
You're looking for
your brother, right?
Have you been following me?!
You just watched quietly while Al was kidnapped?!
We are pursuing them as well.
We couldn't allow your brother's safety to take top priority.
Don't give me that!
We are about to raid the Chimeras' stronghold.
He should be there too.
Tell me where this place is!
A bar called "Devil's Nest."
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
You can't just start whaling on us
without any warning.
Are you the one in charge?
You're looking after
one of mine, aren't you?
You're going to
let me take him home.
No can do.
I see...
Really... everything
you do is so sudden.
You didn't break
your fingers, did you?
Sensei!
That's a pretty unusual body
you've got there.
I suppose.
It won't be all that easy for you to inflict even a single injury on me.
Oh, yeah?
In that case, I'm going to start taking this seriously, too.
Sensei! Is Brother around?!
That's what I'd like to know!
I mean, you two can't even
run a decent errand for me!
Brace yourself, because afterward,
you're going to get a proper scolding!
I-I'm sorry!
No transmutation circle?!
You're not going to dodge me?
I'm not given to raising
my hand against women.
I just...
want to learn the secret of his transmutation.
And when you do?
Gain eternal life,
and then everything else.
This isn't going anywhere.
You got him!
Like I said,
it won't be all that easy for you to inflict even a single injury on me.
Dear...
I've had enough
of just looking on.
I'm not...
about to...
lose one of my children...
again.
Yeah.
My, my, are you still planning to go at it some more?
There you are!
Izumi!
Sensei!
You've overdone it there, sweetheart.
Okay, you're going to cease your futile resistance.
I don't wanna have to do this,
but if you resist,
you know what happens.
You get your filthy hands off of her!
On the double! Fifth and Seventh Squads,
cover the rear entrance!
Third and Ninth Squads,
seal off the area around the bar.
The rest of you, take the front!
Now we've got the older brother, huh?
We've got our whole cast together.
Tucker?
Edward-kun...
You too?
You'll pay for this!
Not only have you kidnapped Al,
but you've gone and hurt Sensei, too!
Hey now, if you would just tell me how to bond a spirit, I'll just—
Shut up!
You're going to return both Al and Sensei to me!
Be careful, Brother!
That man is a homunculus!
Is that right?
Look, I've got a hostage right here.
No wonder!
Sheesh, would all of you
just listen to me?!
Sensei!
Ed!
Right!
Like I said,
I'm the Mightiest Shield.
Sensei!
Izumi!
Now hold on!
This is a one-on-one fight.
Take care of Sensei.
Yeah.
If you want to defeat me,
then fight with
the intent to kill me.
Yeah.
I'm going to send you flying, no matter what!
Ready to storm in
through the back door.
The alley has been sealed off.
Ready to charge in!
That won't work!
For crying out loud...
I had no idea you guys were this hard to get through to!
What?
You even committed a taboo
in order to obtain what you wanted.
As someone so loyal
to their desires,
I didn't think it would be so hard for you to understand me.
Don't you lump me in with the likes of you!
We're the same.
Whether we're homunculus or human, it doesn't matter.
We live only to be devoted to our desires, don't we?
Not me!
I know about how you are now
looking for the Philosopher's Stone.
I don't care about
the Philosopher's Stone.
I just want to return Al—
my brother—to his original form!
He'd be better off
staying the way he is.
What do you know?!
Don't you presume to decide that for us!
I have no intention of negotiating.
If you homunculi are born of
the errors made by us alchemists,
then we alchemists will just
have to correct those errors.
Is that a fact?
This kind of turns me into an ugly man,
so I was hoping not to have to show it to you.
But out of consideration
for your resolve,
I'm going to take you on seriously.
What is that?
This is my serious mode.
Bring it on!
Barely felt that.
Are you serious?!
The composition and structural material of my body is as normal.
The Mightiest Shield, huh?
You've never killed
someone before, have you?
What do you mean?
I'm saying you don't have the heart to do it.
You won't be able to
defeat me like this.
And that goes for
the other homunculi too.
Let me give you enough heart.
Who the hell are you?!
Hey there.
Greed-san!
Bad news! The military—
Now of all times...
The big show is going to be ruined.
Is this really the time
to be acting so casual?
Don't panic.
There's no one in the military who can do anything to us.
Kimbly...
Why, you! You betrayed me!
Greed-san!
Come on, we're going!
Wait!
Catch you later, boy.
You're not getting away from me!
What is this?
Please do not resist.
Resist? What are you talking—
Lt. Col. Archer is calling for you.
Please come with us.
They're about to take my brother away!
I can't just sit back and—
That is an order.
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Episode 34: "Theory of Greed"
You'll pay for this!
Greed, I will defeat you!